Finding Aid for Alpha Epsilon Iota, Alpha Chapter (University of Michigan) Records, 1902-1973
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Alpha Epsilon Iota, Alpha Chapter (University of Michigan) Records
1902-1973
Alpha Epsilon Iota. Alpha Chapter (University of Michigan)
861077 Bimu F41 2
University of Michigan chapter of a national women’s medical sorority. Minute books, publications and other organizational records.
1 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The record group was deposited by the Alpha Chapter of Alpha Epsilon Iota (donor no. 6720 ) and came to the library in 1981.
The record group is open to research.
Alpha Epsilon Iota, Alpha Chapter, is the University of Michigan chapter of a national women’s medical sorority.
The record group includes minute books, publications and other organizational records.
Subjects:
University of Michigan--Students--Societies, etc.StudentsSocieties, etc.; Women physicians--Michigan.; Women--Michigan--Ann Arbor--Societies and clubs.; Greek letter societies--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; Physicians--Michigan.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
African Americans--Women.; Alpha Epsilon Iota. Alpha Chapter (University of Michigan); Christmas.; Clothing and dress.; Fraternities and sororities.; Interiors.; Parties.; Pets.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1961-1970.StudentsSocial life and customs1961-1970.; University of Michigan--Student housing--1961-1970.1961-1970.Student housing; Women college students--Michigan--Ann Arbor.; University of Michigan--Students.Students.
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Chapter records
  - By-laws and articles of incorporation, 1 volumes; 1 folders (Box 1)
  - Minute books
    - 1902-1905 (Box 1)
    - 1905-1922 (Box 1)
    - 1922-1930 (Box 1)
    - 1930-1943 (Box 1)
    - 1937-1951 (Box 1)
  - Officers' reports, 1928-1940 (Box 1)
  - Vice president's handbook (Box 1)
  - Annual reports of Grand Chapter Meetings, 1904-1936 (scattered dates) (Box 1)
  - Ritual books, 2 volumes; 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Visitor's book, 1915-1930 (Box 1)
  - Gift book, 1921-1956 (Box 1)
  - House regulations (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1944; 1962-1973 (Box 1)
  - Membership lists (Box 1)
  - Legal documents (Box 1)
  - Newsletters, 1922-1969 (Box 1)
  - Clippings (Box 1)
  - Photographs (Box 1)
- Publications
  - Journal
    - 1923 (Box 1)
    - 1932 (Box 1)
  - Directory-Journal
    - 1938 (Box 1)
    - 1940 (Box 1)
    - 1944 (Box 1)
    - 1946 (Box 1)
    - 1948 (Box 1)
    - 1950 (Box 1)
    - 1958 (Box 1)
  - Chapter Officers' Handbook
    - 1941 (Box 1)
    - 1946 (Box 1)
  - Constitution and Statutes
    - 1915 (Box 1)
    - 1944 (Box 1)
    - 1951 (Box 1)